originalmockups.com 2019-12-18

# Privacy policy – Original Mockups

LAST UPDATED: Mar 12, 2019

Graphic Market, Inc. (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates the [originalmockups.com](http://originalmockups.com/) website (the “Service”). We know that you care how information about you is used and shared. This Privacy Policy explains what information of yours will be collected by Graphic Market when you use the Graphic Market Service, how the information will be used, and how you can control the collection, correction and/or deletion of information.

PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT CAREFULLY. BY ACCESSING OR USING OUR WEBSITE, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTAND, AND AGREE TO BE BOUND TO ALL THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT AND OUR WEBSITE TERMS OF USE. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THESE TERMS, EXIT THIS PAGE AND DO NOT ACCESS OR USE THE WEBSITE.

### Information We Collect

User-Provided Information: You provide us information about yourself, such as your name, e-mail address, and other personally identifiable information (all referred to as "Personal Information") if you register for a User account with the Service (including by "following," "liking,”, linking your account to the Graphic Market service, etc., on a third party website or network). If you correspond with us by email, we may retain the content of your email messages, your email address, and our responses. We may also retain any messages you send through the Service. You may provide us information in User Content, such as your public profile and comments that you post to the Service.

**Information Collected Through Cookies And Other Technology** : When you visit the Service, we use cookies and related technologies to identify your browser. Please see here for Information About Our Use of Cookies And Similar Technologies.

**Log File Information** : Log file information is automatically reported by your browser each time you access a web page. Please see here for Information [About Our Use of Cookies And Similar Technologies](https://originalmockups.com/support/cookiepolicy).

**Third Party Analytics Services** : Graphic Market uses third party analytics services. See here for how Google uses data when you use our Service and how you may opt-out ([www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](https://originalmockups.com/www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/)). We also use [Algolia Analytics](https://www.algolia.com/policies/privacy). [Please see here for Information About Our Use of Cookies And Similar Technologies](https://originalmockups.com/support/cookiepolicy).

**Social Network and Platform Integration** : The Service may be integrated with social media networks and other platforms (e.g., Facebook, Pinterest, Twitter, Amazon, Google Plus and LinkedIn) whereby information may be shared between us and those platforms. For instance, if you interact with our Service through a social media feature such as a plug-in, then you may be granting us on-going access to certain information from that social media account. If you do not want a social media platform to collect or share information about you, please review the privacy policy and privacy settings of the applicable social media property before using such features on our Service. [Please see here for Information About Our Use of Cookies And Similar Technologies](https://originalmockups.com/support/cookiepolicy).

We will never collect sensitive categories of data such as:

  * Race;
  * Ethnic origin;
  * Politics;
  * Religion;
  * Trade union membership;
  * Genetics;
  * Biometrics (where used for ID purposes);
  * Health;
  * Sex life;
  * Criminal records;
  * Sexual orientation.

### How We Use Your Information

We use the Personal Information you submit or that we collect to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of the Service. We use your information in order to (a) provide you with the Service under our agreement with you and (b) where we have a legitimate interest in doing so to optimize the Service we offer and to let you know about our other products, services, and promotions.

By providing us with your email address (which includes, but is not limited to linking your account to the Graphic Market service on or through a third party website or network such as Facebook), you acknowledge we may use the email address to send you Service-related notices, including any notices required by law, in lieu of communication by postal mail. You also acknowledge that we may send you notifications of activity on the Service to the email address you give us, in accordance with any applicable privacy settings. We may use your email address to send you other messages, such as newsletters, changes to features of the Service, or special offers. If you do not want to receive such email messages, you may opt out in the unsubscribe button that is in the email delivered or change your preferences in your account settings page. Opting out may prevent you from receiving email messages regarding updates, improvements, or offers. You may not opt out of Service-related e-mails.

Following termination or deactivation of your User account, we may retain your profile information and User Content for a commercially reasonable time for backup, archival, contract performance and enforcement, or audit purposes but for no longer than is necessary and only where the information is accurate and relevant for our use. Furthermore, we may retain and continue to use indefinitely all information (including User Content) contained in your communications to other Users or posted to public or semi-public areas of the Service after termination or deactivation of your User account.

We may use certain information about you and/or your User Content internally for purposes such as analyzing how the Service is used, diagnosing service or technical problems, maintaining security, and personalizing content.

We use cookies and log file information as described here: [Information About Our Use of Cookies And Similar Technologies](https://originalmockups.com/support/cookiepolicy).

### How We Share Your Information

Personal Information. We will not rent or sell your Personal Information to others. We may share your Personal Information with third parties (such as hosting providers, payment processors, database providers, customer support providers) for the purpose of providing the Service to you. If we do this, such third parties' will be contractually bound to safeguard your Personal Information. We may store Personal Information in locations outside of our direct control (for instance, on servers or databases co-located with hosting providers) on the basis of an agreement to safeguard your information.

As we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets or business offerings. Customer, email, and visitor information is generally one of the transferred business assets in these types of transactions. We may also transfer or assign such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, or dissolution.

Except as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy, we will not disclose Personal Information to any third party unless required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to:

(a) Conform to the law, comply with legal process served on us or our affiliates, or investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual illegal activities; 

(b) To enforce our Terms of Service, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend ourselves against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, or to protect the security or integrity of our Site; and 

(c) To exercise or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Graphic Market, Inc. Our Users or others. 

**Payment Services.**  We offer PayPal integration. All PayPal transactions are subject to the respective policies, PayPal Privacy Policy available at <https://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full>. We do not control PayPal's use of the data it collects.

Non-Personal Information. We may share non-personally identifiable information (such as anonymous usage data, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with interested third parties to help them understand the usage patterns for certain Graphic Market services.

Deliver targeted advertising to you for our Business Purposes and/or with your Consent. We may use your information to develop and display content and advertising (and work with third parties who do so) tailored to your interests and/or location and to measure its effectiveness. [For more information, see our Cookie Policy](https://originalmockups.com/support/cookiepolicy). 

### How do we handle your social logins?

In Short: If you choose to register or log in to our websites using a social media account, we may have access to certain information about you.

Our Sites may offer you the ability to register and login using your third-party social media account details (like your Facebook or Google Plus logins). Where you choose to do this, we will receive certain profile information about you from your social media provider. The profile Information we receive may vary depending on the social media provider concerned, but will often include your name, e-mail address, profile picture as well as other information you choose to make public. If you log in using Facebook, we may also request access to other permissions related to your accounts, such as friends, check-ins, and likes, and you may choose to grant or deny us access to each individual permission.

We will use the information we receive only for the purposes that are described in this privacy policy or that are otherwise made clear to you on the Sites. Please note that we do not control, and are not responsible for, other uses of your personal information by your third party social media provider. We recommend that you review their privacy policy to understand how they collect, use and share your personal information, and how you can set your privacy preferences on their sites and apps.

### Is your information transferred internationally?  

In Short: We may transfer, store, and process your information in countries other than your own.

Our servers are located in the United States. If you are accessing our Sites from outside the United States, please be aware that your information may be transferred to, stored, and processed by us in our facilities and by those third parties with whom we may share your personal information. 

If you are a resident in the European Economic Area, then these countries may not have data protection or other laws as comprehensive as those in your country. We will, however, take all necessary measures to protect your personal information in accordance with this privacy policy and applicable law. 

### How We Protect Your Information

We care about the integrity and security of your Personal Information and implement appropriate technical and organizational security measures to safeguard your Personal Information. We can’t, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Graphic Market services or guarantee that your information on the Service may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. Your privacy settings may also be affected by changes to the functionality of Graphic Market's distributors, such as social networks. We are not responsible for the functionality or security measures of any third party.

To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps (such as requesting a unique password) to verify your identity before granting you access to your account. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information, and for controlling access to your email communications from Graphic Market, at all times.

### Compromise of Personal Information

In the event that Personal Information is compromised as a result of a breach of security, we will promptly notify those persons whose Personal Information has been compromised, in accordance with the notification procedures set forth in this Privacy Policy, or as otherwise required by applicable law.

### Your Choices About Your Information

**All Users**

  * Decline to Submit Information. You may, of course, decline to submit Personal Information through the Service, in which case Graphic Market may not be able to provide certain services to you.

  * Update Account Information. You may update or correct your account information and email preferences at any time by logging in to your account settings page. You can also exercise any of your rights by contacting us directly at  **support@originalmockups.com**.

  * Unsubscribe from emails. To unsubscribe from a particular newsletter, click the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of that email newsletter. When we send newsletters to subscribers we may allow advertisers or partners to include messages in those newsletters, or we may send dedicated newsletters and marketing messages on behalf of those advertisers or partners. We may disclose your opt-out choices to third parties so that they can honor your preferences in accordance with applicable laws.

  * Options concerning third-party ad networks. For more information about third-party ad networks and services that use these technologies, you can visit [buysellads.com](http://buysellads.com/) and click here to opt out or to learn more about your options. Please see here for Information [About Our Use of Cookies And Similar Technologies](https://originalmockups.com/support/cookiepolicy).

**EEA Residents**

If you are located in the EEA, or if otherwise required by applicable law, you also have the following rights in relation to your information:

  * Inspection and access: you can request from us a summary and a copy of any Personal Information we hold about you;

  * Correction/addition/removal: where you believe your information is inaccurate or incomplete, you are entitled to request us to correct, amend or delete it;

  * Portability: you may request that we send you any Personal Information that you have provided to us or ask that we send this information to a third party;

  * Objection: you may object to us using your Personal Information where we use it based on our legitimate interests to do so;

  * Restriction: you may request that we restrict the processing of your information where you believe it is inaccurate, our processing is unlawful, you believe we no longer need the information or if you have objected to our use of it; and

  * Automated Decision Making: where we undertake automated decision making (including profiling), which significantly affects you, you are entitled to object to such decision-making.

You always have the right to lodge a complaint with the relevant supervisory authority for data protection in your jurisdiction.

### Update your information

If you need to change or correct your Personal Data provided to us or wish to have Personal Data removed from our systems, you can use the built-in functionality, or you may contact us at:

Email: support@originalmockups.com

We will address your requests as required by applicable law.

### Paddle

Paddle are our online payment processor, they collect your information at checkout to process your purchase. Upon checkout there is also an optional check-box to allow us to contact you for marketing purposes. This is opt-in and is compliant with GDPR. If you would like your purchase history deleted please contact us.

Our order process is conducted by our online reseller Paddle.com. Paddle.com is the Merchant of Record for all our orders. Paddle provides all customer service inquiries and handles returns.

You can read more about Paddle and GDPR [here](https://paddle.com/gdpr).

### Changes to this privacy policy

This Privacy Policy is effective as of May 25, 2018, and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page.

We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.

If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us or by placing a prominent notice on our website.

### Contact us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.  
Graphic Market, Inc. 

Carrera 86 #15-25, La Princesa  
+57 (5) 646-1345, +57 (300) 810-2808  
Cartagena 130010  
Colombia.  
Email: support@originalmockups.com
